<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title>All Posts - Rómulo García</title>
        <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/</link>
        <description>All Posts | Rómulo García</description>
        <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 10:00:00 &#43;0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/posts/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" /><item>
    <title>Bachelor Thesis: Using of Deep Gaussian Processes for Wind Energy Prediction</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/tfg/</link>
    <pubDate>Sun, 05 Mar 2023 15:58:26 &#43;0800</pubDate>
    <author>Rómulo García</author>
    <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/tfg/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[<p>Bachelor Thesis focused on testing Gaussian Processes and Deep Gaussian Processes to predict
wind energy production. Our experiments will take place in Sotavento, a wind mill complex located in the North of Spain. Wind energy is not constant, the wind mills don’t operate at certain speeds, the infrastructures require a lot of space&hellip;</p>
<p>Therefore, these predictions are crucial as they can avoid power shortages, provide the basis for making decisions in power system planning and operation, between many other positive applications. We are going to use Gaussian processes as they can scale to very large datasets, and are non parametric. Moreover, the deep Gaussian processes approach increases their flexibility and precision.</p>]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>Basic 3D Engine</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/infogr/</link>
    <pubDate>Thu, 05 May 2022 15:58:26 &#43;0800</pubDate>
    <author>Rómulo García</author>
    <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/infogr/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[<p>First assignment consisting of a Whitted-style ray tracer. This is a
recursive rendering algorithm for determining light transport between one or
more light sources and a camera, via scene surfaces, by tracing rays backwards
into the scene, starting at the camera.</p>
<p></p>
<p>Second assignment consisting of a basic 3D engine. The 3D engine is a tool
to visualize a scene graph: a hierarchy of meshes, each of which can have a unique
local transform. Each mesh will have a texture and a shader. The input for the
shader includes a set of light sources. The shading model implemented in the
fragment shader determines the response of the materials to these lights. Moreover, some postprocessing techniques such as anti-aliasing are also implemented.</p>]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>One Song A Day</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/onesongaday/</link>
    <pubDate>Fri, 05 Feb 2021 15:58:26 &#43;0800</pubDate>
    <author>Rómulo García</author>
    <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/onesongaday/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[<p>AI Song recommendation android application based on user song reviews. The application was made using Android Studio (Java) and Firebase. A Python server-side application was developed to manage data and populate the database.</p>
<p></p>
<p><a href="https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.rogarmu8.onesongaday" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreffer ">Google Play Link</a></p>]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>E-Ink Google Calendar</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/googlecalendar/</link>
    <pubDate>Tue, 05 Jan 2021 15:58:26 &#43;0800</pubDate>
    <author>Rómulo García</author>
    <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/googlecalendar/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[<p>E-ink display that connects to your google calendar and retrieves the data from the next 6 days updating every 24 hours.</p>
<h1 id="parts-used">Parts used:</h1>
<ul>
<li><a href="https://www.waveshare.com/wiki/E-Paper_ESP32_Driver_Board" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreffer ">https://www.waveshare.com/wiki/E-Paper_ESP32_Driver_Board</a></li>
<li><a href="https://www.waveshare.com/product/7.5inch-e-paper.htm" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreffer ">https://www.waveshare.com/product/7.5inch-e-paper.htm</a></li>
</ul>
<h1 id="explanation">Explanation:</h1>
<ul>
<li>We use google scripts to connect to our google calendar and retrieve the needed information.</li>
<li>After doing such, from our esp32 we connect to the scripts application and retrieve the data from the html reponse.</li>
<li>We give format to the response to have a better integrationwith the e-ink display.</li>
<li>We print it to the display using the waveshare library for arduino. (Make sure you have all libraries and drivers download and installed correctly to be able to connect to the display)</li>
<li>The data will update every 24 Hours, restarting the device will force an update at any time.</li>
</ul>
<h1 id="example-of-data-retrieved-from-google-scripts">Example of data retrieved from google scripts:</h1>
<p>Sat May 08 2021
Lunch with friends                  14:30:00-15:30:00
Dinner with friends                 21:00:00-22:00:00
|
Sun May 09 2021
Breakfast                           9:30:00-10:30:00
|
Mon May 10 2021
Going to class                      All day
|
Tue May 11 2021
Computer Science Exam               10:00:00-12:00:00
|
Wed May 12 2021
Studying for next exam              All day
|
Thu May 13 2021
Reading                             21:30:00-22:00:00</p>]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>Clicky Code</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/clickycode/</link>
    <pubDate>Thu, 05 Mar 2020 15:58:26 &#43;0800</pubDate>
    <author>Rómulo García</author>
    <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/clickycode/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[<p>Clicker video game with room decoration management. Game made with Unity(C#), Photoshop, Bosca Ceoil.</p>
<p></p>
<p><a href="https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.rogarmu8.clickycode" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreffer ">Google Play Link</a></p>]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>Fallen Dots</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/fallendots/</link>
    <pubDate>Fri, 05 Aug 2016 15:58:26 &#43;0800</pubDate>
    <author>Rómulo García</author>
    <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/fallendots/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[<p>Simple video game based on reflexes. Game made with Gdevelop.</p>
<p></p>
<p><a href="https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.rogarmu8Games.FallenDots" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreffer ">Google Play Link</a></p>]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>Cifras del Mundo</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/cifrasdelmundo/</link>
    <pubDate>Sun, 10 Dec 2023 10:00:00 &#43;0800</pubDate>
    <author>Rómulo García</author>
    <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/cifrasdelmundo/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[<p>Cifras del Mundo is an engaging numeric trivia game that tests players&rsquo; knowledge of global statistics and facts. Developed over a single weekend, it offers a fun and educational experience for trivia enthusiasts.</p>
<h1 id="key-features">Key Features</h1>
<ul>
<li><strong>Multiplayer Mode</strong>: Compete with friends and other players worldwide</li>
<li><strong>Diverse Question Bank</strong>: Features a wide range of questions covering various global statistics</li>
<li><strong>User-Friendly Interface</strong>: Designed for an engaging and seamless gaming experience</li>
<li><strong>Quick Development</strong>: Built in just one weekend, showcasing rapid development capabilities</li>
</ul>
<h1 id="gameplay">Gameplay</h1>
<p>Players answer numeric questions about global facts and statistics, making it both entertaining and educational. The game provides an excellent way to learn interesting numerical information about the world.</p>]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>NutrAI</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/nutrai/</link>
    <pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 10:00:00 &#43;0800</pubDate>
    <author>Rómulo García</author>
    <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/nutrai/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[<p>NutrAI is an AI-driven nutrition planning tool designed for nutritionists, fitness coaches, and health professionals. It enables the creation of personalized meal plans in seconds, adapting to client preferences with real-time updates.</p>
<h1 id="key-features">Key Features</h1>
<ul>
<li><strong>AI Plan Generator</strong>: Quickly generates meal plans tailored to client needs</li>
<li><strong>Extensive Meal Database</strong>: Offers a vast array of meals, with the option to add custom recipes</li>
<li><strong>Interactive Plans</strong>: Provides accessible plans with user feedback mechanisms</li>
<li><strong>PDF Export</strong>: Allows creation of customizable meal plan copies in different languages</li>
<li><strong>Client Management</strong>: Centralizes contact information and communication tools</li>
<li><strong>Progress Tracking</strong>: Facilitates data-driven adjustments based on client results</li>
</ul>
<video controls poster="https://storage.googleapis.com/nutrai-videos/play.webp" style="width: 100%; height: auto;">
  <source src="https://storage.googleapis.com/nutrai-videos/nutrai_v3_en.webm" type="video/webm">
</video>
<p><a href="https://www.nutrai.app" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreffer ">Visit NutrAI</a></p>]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>OneReferral</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/onereferral/</link>
    <pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 10:00:00 &#43;0800</pubDate>
    <author>Rómulo García</author>
    <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/onereferral/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[<p>OneReferral provides a straightforward, one-time payment referral system designed exclusively for Stripe users. By leveraging satisfied customers, businesses can reduce acquisition costs and foster growth through personal recommendations.</p>
<h1 id="key-features">Key Features</h1>
<ul>
<li><strong>Dashboard</strong>: Manage customers, campaigns, and track progress with intuitive charts</li>
<li><strong>Diverse Campaigns</strong>: Create campaigns with limited duration discounts, maximum stacking discounts, and support for different currencies</li>
<li><strong>Stripe Integration</strong>: Utilizes Stripe Promo Codes as referral code inputs for seamless integration</li>
<li><strong>Lifetime Access</strong>: Offers a pay-once, access-forever model with options for single projects or unlimited projects</li>
</ul>
<p><a href="https://www.onereferral.app" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreffer ">Visit OneReferral</a></p>]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>100 Vibe Coding</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/100vibecoding/</link>
    <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 10:00:00 &#43;0800</pubDate>
    <author>Rómulo García</author>
    <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/100vibecoding/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[<p>100 Vibe Coding is an innovative platform that leverages AI to help users build project ideas through 100 progressive challenges. It focuses on mastering the art of prompting and accelerating project development.</p>
<h1 id="key-features">Key Features</h1>
<ul>
<li><strong>Progressive Challenges</strong>: Engage with 100 challenges that adapt to your coding style</li>
<li><strong>Sandbox Environment</strong>: Test ideas and build projects in an interactive sandbox</li>
<li><strong>Real-Time Feedback</strong>: Receive immediate feedback to enhance learning</li>
<li><strong>Gamified Experience</strong>: Enjoy an engaging, game-like learning journey</li>
<li><strong>Project Showcase</strong>: Explore projects built using Vibe Coding</li>
</ul>
<h1 id="getting-started">Getting Started</h1>
<p>Start with 10 free challenges without requiring a credit card. The platform offers a comprehensive learning experience that teaches users to harness AI in programming effectively.</p>]]></description>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
