<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title>Rómulo García</title>
        <link>https://rogarmu8.github.io/</link>
        <description>Rómulo García Portfolio</description>
        <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><managingEditor>rogarmu8@gmail.com (Rómulo García Mus)</managingEditor>
            <webMaster>rogarmu8@gmail.com (Rómulo García Mus)</webMaster><lastBuildDate>Sun, 05 Mar 2023 15:58:26 &#43;0800</lastBuildDate>
            <atom:link href="https://rogarmu8.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
        <item>
    <title>Bachelor Thesis: Using of Deep Gaussian Processes for Wind Energy Prediction</title>
    <link>https://rogarmu8.github.io/posts/tfg/</link>
    <pubDate>Sun, 05 Mar 2023 15:58:26 &#43;0800</pubDate>
    <author>Rómulo García</author>
    <guid>https://rogarmu8.github.io/posts/tfg/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[Bachelor Thesis focused on testing Gaussian Processes and Deep Gaussian Processes to predict wind energy production. Our experiments will take place in Sotavento, a wind mill complex located in the North of Spain. Wind energy is not constant, the wind mills don’t operate at certain speeds, the infrastructures require a lot of space&hellip;
Therefore, these predictions are crucial as they can avoid power shortages, provide the basis for making decisions in power system planning and operation, between many other positive applications.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>Basic 3D Engine</title>
    <link>https://rogarmu8.github.io/posts/infogr/</link>
    <pubDate>Thu, 05 May 2022 15:58:26 &#43;0800</pubDate>
    <author>Rómulo García</author>
    <guid>https://rogarmu8.github.io/posts/infogr/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[First assignment consisting of a Whitted-style ray tracer. This is a recursive rendering algorithm for determining light transport between one or more light sources and a camera, via scene surfaces, by tracing rays backwards into the scene, starting at the camera.
Second assignment consisting of a basic 3D engine. The 3D engine is a tool to visualize a scene graph: a hierarchy of meshes, each of which can have a unique local transform.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>One Song A Day</title>
    <link>https://rogarmu8.github.io/posts/onesongaday/</link>
    <pubDate>Fri, 05 Feb 2021 15:58:26 &#43;0800</pubDate>
    <author>Rómulo García</author>
    <guid>https://rogarmu8.github.io/posts/onesongaday/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[AI Song recommendation android application based on user song reviews. The application was made using Android Studio (Java) and Firebase. A Python server-side application was developed to manage data and populate the database.
Google Play Link ]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>E-Ink Google Calendar</title>
    <link>https://rogarmu8.github.io/posts/googlecalendar/</link>
    <pubDate>Tue, 05 Jan 2021 15:58:26 &#43;0800</pubDate>
    <author>Rómulo García</author>
    <guid>https://rogarmu8.github.io/posts/googlecalendar/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[E-ink display that connects to your google calendar and retrieves the data from the next 6 days updating every 24 hours.
Parts used: https://www.waveshare.com/wiki/E-Paper_ESP32_Driver_Board https://www.waveshare.com/product/7.5inch-e-paper.htm Explanation: We use google scripts to connect to our google calendar and retrieve the needed information. After doing such, from our esp32 we connect to the scripts application and retrieve the data from the html reponse. We give format to the response to have a better integrationwith the e-ink display.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>Clicky Code</title>
    <link>https://rogarmu8.github.io/posts/clickycode/</link>
    <pubDate>Thu, 05 Mar 2020 15:58:26 &#43;0800</pubDate>
    <author>Rómulo García</author>
    <guid>https://rogarmu8.github.io/posts/clickycode/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[Clicker video game with room decoration management. Game made with Unity(C#), Photoshop, Bosca Ceoil.
Google Play Link ]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>Fallen Dots</title>
    <link>https://rogarmu8.github.io/posts/fallendots/</link>
    <pubDate>Fri, 05 Aug 2016 15:58:26 &#43;0800</pubDate>
    <author>Rómulo García</author>
    <guid>https://rogarmu8.github.io/posts/fallendots/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[Simple video game based on reflexes. Game made with Gdevelop.
Google Play Link ]]></description>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
